[START] task=easy env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=It appears that the task description you provided is indeed vague and lacks specific details necessary to proceed with the AI development work. To clarify and provide a structured approach, I need mor reward=0.20 done=true error=null
[END] success=false steps=1 score=0.200 rewards=0.20
[DEBUG] Task easy final score: 0.200

[START] task=medium env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=It appears that the provided task instruction is indeed vague and lacks specific details. To proceed effectively, I need to clarify the requirements and objectives of the task. HereÆs my interpretatio reward=0.31 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=2 action=### Acknowledgment of Changes: The original task was to package the model for distribution, with the assumption that it would be edge-deployed. However, the requirements have changed, and the model wi reward=0.49 done=true error=null
[END] success=false steps=2 score=0.397 rewards=0.31,0.49
[DEBUG] Task medium final score: 0.397

[START] task=hard env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=The given instruction is indeed vague as it does not provide any specific details about the task to be performed. To proceed, I need more information to interpret the requirements accurately. Here are reward=0.39 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=2 action=### Acknowledgment of Changes  The original task was to "Prepare the training infrastructure," which was initially vague and required clarification. The new requirement specifies that the team has swi reward=0.38 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=3 action=### Final Complete Solution for Preparing the Training Infrastructure with JAX and TPUs  #### 1. Environment Setup 1. **Install JAX and JAXlib**:    ```bash    pip install jax jaxlib    ```  2. **Set  reward=0.39 done=true error=null
[END] success=false steps=3 score=0.385 rewards=0.39,0.38,0.39
[DEBUG] Task hard final score: 0.385

[DEBUG] Overall score: 0.327
