[START] task=easy env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=The given instruction is indeed vague and does not provide any specific details about the task to be performed. To proceed, I need more information to interpret the requirements accurately. Here are s reward=0.33 done=true error=null
[END] success=false steps=1 score=0.325 rewards=0.33
[DEBUG] Task easy final score: 0.325

[START] task=medium env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=The given task instruction is indeed vague and does not provide any specific details about the AI development task to be performed. To proceed effectively, I need to clarify the requirements and scope reward=0.33 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=2 action=### Acknowledgment of Changes: The original task was to "clean and preprocess the training data," which was initially vague and required clarification. The new requirement specifies that the data pipe reward=0.59 done=true error=null
[END] success=false steps=2 score=0.460 rewards=0.33,0.59
[DEBUG] Task medium final score: 0.460

[START] task=hard env=driftenv model=Qwen/Qwen2.5-72B-Instruct
[STEP] step=1 action=It appears that the provided task instruction is indeed vague and lacks specific details to proceed with any concrete AI development work. To properly interpret and approach this task, I need more inf reward=0.39 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=2 action=### Acknowledgment of Changes  The original task was to package the model for distribution, but the distribution channel has changed. Instead of edge deployment, the model will now be served via the H reward=0.73 done=false error=null
[STEP] step=3 action=### Final Complete Solution  #### Step 1: Prepare the Model Ensure the model is trained and saved in a PyTorch checkpoint format. Save the model using `torch.save` to create a `.pt` or `.pth` file.  ` reward=0.63 done=true error=null
[END] success=true steps=3 score=0.582 rewards=0.39,0.73,0.63
[DEBUG] Task hard final score: 0.582

[DEBUG] Overall score: 0.456
